{
    "id": "fdec9b487e31485dafb0f455ae4efea3",
    "title": "Each vs. Every",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "4ac6757ffbf0459a9c3421d4cb6c86a4",
            "title": "Each vs. Every",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "You have to change the sheets .......................... other day.",
                    "description": "Every is used with expressions like other, few and numbers.",
                    "answers": [
                        "each",
                        "every",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Buses leave .......................... ten minutes.",
                    "description": "Every can be used before a plural noun in expressions that refer to intervals. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "each",
                        "every",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................ team in a cricket game has 11 players.",
                    "description": "Each is used to talk about two or more things. Every is used to talk about three or more things.Ever",
                    "answers": [
                        "Each",
                        "Every",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".......................... of them was given a present.",
                    "description": "Every cannot be used before a pronoun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Each",
                        "Every",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I could understand ........................... word she said.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "each",
                        "every",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The four students ........................... received a laptop.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "each",
                        "every",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She kissed them ............................... on the forehead.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "each",
                        "every",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is ............................ chance that we will win.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "every",
                        "each",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................ of them was asked to speak for a few minutes.",
                    "description": "Every cannot be used before a pronoun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Each",
                        "Every",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I visit my grandparents .............................. now and then.",
                    "description": "Every is used in expressions like every now and then.",
                    "answers": [
                        "every",
                        "each",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have written to ................................ friend I have.",
                    "description": "Either could be used here",
                    "answers": [
                        "every",
                        "each",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Almost ............................. child in cities receives school education.",
                    "description": "Each cannot be used with expressions like almost, nearly, practically or without exception.",
                    "answers": [
                        "every",
                        "each",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}